(Sheldon:)What if a simulated van rear-ends me?
(Penny:)I'll hit you in the face with a pillow.
[ENGINE STARTS ON SIMULATOR]
(Leonard:)Okay, now shift into drive.
And pull out slowly into traffic.
[TIRES SCREECHING ON SIMULATOR]
Do you...? Watch the...
- Watch out for the pedestrians!
- Oh, God, wait.
[GIRL SCREAMS ON SIMULATOR]
Hit the brakes! Hit the brakes!
[TIRES SCREECH ON SIMULATOR]
[CAR CRASHES ON SIMULATOR]
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
[CAR CRASHES THEN MAN YELLS
ON SIMULATOR]
Sorry. Excuse me.
[TIRES SCREECH THEN CAR CRASHES
ON SIMULATOR]
(Sheldon:)My bad.
[TIRES SCREECH THEN GLASS SHATTERS
ON SIMULATOR]
(Sheldon:)Student driver.
(Leonard:)How did you manage to get on
the second floor of the Glendale Galleria?